Accidental physical contact
Energy crystal power increased by 1%
A hug increased it by 3%
A kiss raised it by 10%
The spaceship was damaged during its landing on Earth
To contact Lanke Star,
we must fully recharge the energy crystals.
Now I have to get her to kiss me.
Hao Ruichi.
I’m going out to buy something.
Do you need anything?
Why didn’t you knock before coming in?
So our little Ruichi has this kind of hobby, huh?
Well, I won’t disturb you then.
Carry on.
Good luck.
Keep it up.
You can do it.
No way.
How could I, a noble envoy, beg for a kiss from someone like this?
I need to think of a plan.
This won’t work.
I must quickly think of a way to execute the plan.
What are you doing?
I...
I’m getting my coat to go out with you.
Crazy.
So strange.
Isn’t this how it always goes in movies?
Why doesn’t the wall slam trick work at all?
Usually, you don’t even want to step out of the door.
What’s gotten into you today?
Coming out shopping with me?
Sometimes, going out for a stroll
to learn about the life of Earthlings
is quite nice too.
Our little Ruichi is becoming more sensible.
If you call me little Ruichi one more time,
I’ll take you back to Lanke Star for research!
Oh, I’m so scared.
Sorry.
For the greater good,
I have to do this.
No, no...
Are you okay?
Who threw this soda can?
Such bad manners.
Damn it.
Just a little more.
No way.
I can't hesitate anymore.
I need to replenish my energy first.
I...
What's wrong with you?
Forget it.
I better just tell her the truth.
Qi Miao...
I need to talk to you.
Go ahead.
Actually, that accidental kiss we had...
unexpectedly replenished the energy in my crystal.
I suspect...
that kissing you...
is a way to recharge my energy crystal.
So I was thinking...
Um...
Hao Ruichi!
Come quickly!
Here!
Come and try this!
It's an ice magic treat from Earth!
Go ahead, try it!
Are you stupid?
Ice cream is meant to be eaten slowly, bit by bit.
Look, like this.
What’s wrong with you?
Because of that kiss earlier...
my crystal got recharged with energy.
So I thought...
What do you mean, 'so you thought'?!
Do you even know this kind of behavior...
is considered harassment here on Earth?!
The last person who did something like this...
got locked up already.
You're insane.
Weird...
Why didn’t the crystal react this time?
Could I have been wrong?
What is this?
This food is terrible.
Hey, boss!
Is this dish even meant for people?!
What's wrong?
Is there something you're not satisfied with?
Satisfied.
Take a good look yourself.
I ordered spicy chicken with diced chili.
You put so much meat in it,
and not a single chili.
Tell me,
how am I supposed to be satisfied?
Sorry.
Since you're the
very first official customers of our place,
I thought I'd be generous with the portions.
No, no.
Your food tastes this bad,
how dare you even think of opening a restaurant like others?
My apologies.
I'm really sorry.
How about I make a fresh plate for you?
Forget it. I've lost my appetite.
Then, how about I waive the bill for this meal?
Let's call it a grand opening promotion, okay?
Is waiving the bill enough?
After eating something this bad,
tell me,
who's going to compensate for the emotional damage?
What's going on here, you two?
What's going on?
Who cooked this dish?
Why does it taste so awful?
The dish was cooked by me.
From the smell of cooking oil on you both,
and the grease stains on your cuffs,
I can tell
that the two of you
are also running a restaurant, right?
So what?
Just because we own a restaurant we can't be customers?
As someone who also creates delicious food
to bring happiness to others,
how could you act so dishonorably
to bully your peers like this?
Are you out of your mind?
Enough.
Today just isn't our day.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
The food someone puts their whole heart into making
shouldn't be insulted like this.
This guy must have watched too many dramas.
Bro, let's go.
Why don't you try it yourself to see if it tastes bad?
Alright.
I'll eat it.
It's fine.
I'm just hungry anyway.
I don't think it tastes bad.
What in the world...
This guy is clearly not right in the head.
Let's go.
Ait!
Are you okay?
Idiot.
Why do you even bother with people like that?
If you don't teach them a lesson,
they'll just come back next time.
Ait!
Do you think I'm really not cut out to be a cook?
Don't doubt yourself.
This is just a necessary step
on the road to pursuing culinary excellence.
Do you understand?
Um...
Our shop just opened,
so I'll head out to hand out some flyers.
I'll do it.
This is a good chance for you to practice more.
Alright.
I never expected
her to actually be this cute.
No. 18 Sakura Street.
If someone shows interest in this jade,
tell them to go to No. 18 Sakura Street
and find Boss Qi.
Hao Ruichi should be somewhere nearby.
So he really is here.
How exactly do I replenish my energy?
Could his crystal be damaged too?